[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "name": "Gumroad",
    "revenue": 21200000,
    "problem": "Creating a website to sell something is confusing and hard to set up for beginners or non-technical people.",
    "solution": "Super-simple e-commerce tool for digital content creators",
    "developer": "Sahil Lavingia",
    "ideation": "Scratching his own itch",
    "mvp": "Built in one weekend",
    "growth1": "Cold email",
    "growth2": "Email List",
    "industry": "E-commerce",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "Free",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Gumroad is free to use, they charge a 10% fee of the sales",
    "traffic": 22620000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.07810197465,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "I Started Gumroad as a Weekend Project and Now It’s Making $350k/Mo - - Gumroad in Q2 2023"
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "name": "GMass",
    "revenue": 5400000,
    "problem": "Sending a high volume of email campaigns from within Gmail is difficult",
    "solution": "A Gmail plugin that allows you to send cold emails and email marketing campaigns with Gmail",
    "developer": "Ajay Goel ",
    "ideation": "An internal tool to manage his business easily.",
    "mvp": "Built in two weeks",
    "growth1": "Reddit",
    "growth2": "Reddit",
    "industry": "Sales",
    "platform": "Gmail",
    "productType": "Extension",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "3 plans priced at $19, $29,  and $49 respectively",
    "traffic": 678203,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.6635181502,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "How I Launched A $200K/Month Gmail Mail Merge Tool"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "name": "Tweet Hunter",
    "revenue": 2640000,
    "problem": "Building and monetizing Twitter audience can take so long",
    "solution": "Twitter tool focused on helping users build and monetize their audiences",
    "developer": "Tibault Louis-Lucas ",
    "ideation": "Inspired by his unsuccessful tweets",
    "mvp": "Built in a week",
    "growth1": "Twitter",
    "growth2": "Twitter",
    "industry": "Social Media",
    "platform": "Twitter",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2C",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Tweet Hunter plans start at $48/mo",
    "traffic": 616255,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.3569950751,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "My \"Failed Tweets\" Inspired Me To Launch A $492K/Year Twitter Growth Tool"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "name": "Prerender.io",
    "revenue": 2640000,
    "problem": "Getting Google to properly crawl and index dynamic content can be a nightmare for beginners. ",
    "solution": "Allows search engines to crawl SEO-friendly versions of React, Angular, and Javascript websites",
    "developer": "Todd Hooper",
    "ideation": "Scratching his own itch",
    "mvp": "Built in one weekend",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Software",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$199 - $399",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Free, $90/mo, $290/mo",
    "traffic": 86206,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 2.552026541,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "How I Bootstrapped My SaaS Company To $2.5M/Year In 5 Years As A Solo Founder"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "name": "Carrd",
    "revenue": 1200000,
    "problem": "Building a simple, responsive one-page websites is often hectic for non-technical people",
    "solution": "Single-page responsive site builder",
    "developer": "AJ",
    "ideation": "He built it for fun - it was something he needed for himself",
    "mvp": "Built in 9 months",
    "growth1": "Twitter",
    "growth2": "Twitter",
    "industry": "Software",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Offers a free plan and three paid options priced at $9, $19, and $49 per year; based on the number of sites you can build ",
    "traffic": 16400000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.006097560976,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "The SaaS Company That Accidentally Grew to 800,000 Users - Carrd: How to make $4k/mo from a side project"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "name": "Plausible",
    "revenue": 1200000,
    "problem": "Google Analytics is frustrating to use, difficult to understand, slow to load and privacy-invasive.",
    "solution": "Easy to use and privacy-friendly Google Analytics alternative ",
    "developer": "Marko Saric",
    "ideation": "The founder had a really bad experience with Google and its products and was like, \"Nope, I'm out.\" They wanted to find a different, more ethical tool.",
    "mvp": "Built in a month",
    "growth1": "Content Marketing",
    "growth2": "Content Marketing",
    "industry": "Software",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Plans start at $9 and $19 per month, and grow as the pageviews increase",
    "traffic": 487738,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.2050281094,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "How we built a $1M ARR open source SaaS - Bootstrapping a privacy-first Google Analytics alternative to $4k/mo"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "name": "Taplio",
    "revenue": 1080000,
    "problem": "Growing an audience on LinkedIn and converting them into business opportunities is a challenging task.\r\n",
    "solution": "Linkedin content generation and scheduling tool",
    "developer": "Thibault Louis-Lucas",
    "ideation": "Inspired by their success building a twitter product (Tweet Hunter), they replicated a LinkedIn-focused tool. ",
    "mvp": "Built in a week",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Social Media",
    "platform": "Linkedin",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2C",
    "priceRange": "$49 - $99",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Three plans: $39, $52, and $149 per month",
    "traffic": 1041000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.08645533141,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "How We Built A $3.5M ARR LinkedIn Tool That Will Be Acquired For $10M-$15M"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "name": "Rootd",
    "revenue": 1000000,
    "problem": "Coping with anxiety and panic attacks can be overwhelming.",
    "solution": "A mobile app that helps people manage their panic attacks",
    "developer": "Ania Wysocka",
    "ideation": "Personal experience - She couldnt find an app to help her cope with anxiety and panic attacks, she built one.",
    "mvp": "Built in a few months",
    "growth1": "App Store",
    "growth2": "App Store",
    "industry": "Wellness",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Mobile App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$99 - $199",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Three Tiers: $9.99/month, $79.99/year, $199/lifetime\nCustomer Plan for Companies",
    "traffic": 5000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 16.66666667,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "I Built An App That Helps People Manage Panic Attacks [2M+ Users]"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "name": "Tally",
    "revenue": 840000,
    "problem": "Builders and no-coders want a simple, yet powerful form builder with countless limits and paywalls.",
    "solution": "Simple form builder for makers and no-coders",
    "developer": "Marie Martens ",
    "ideation": "Could not find the right tool to create forms - Settled on creating a fast, seamless, and fun-filled form-building tool for coders\n",
    "mvp": "Built in two months",
    "growth1": "Product Hunt",
    "growth2": "Product Hunt",
    "industry": "Software",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$49 - $99",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "99% of Tally's features are available to free and paid users. The paid plan costs $29/month or $290/year",
    "traffic": 4730000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.01479915433,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "Year 1: Getting our first users and launching on Product Hunt - Bootstrapping to $10K MRR through product-led growth - Reaching $60K MRR with a team of 4"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "name": "CASTANET",
    "revenue": 732000,
    "problem": "Manual LinkedIn lead generation is a time-consuming process that requires consistent effort.",
    "solution": "A LinkedIn outreach automation tool ",
    "developer": "Mac Martine",
    "ideation": "He brainstormed with business owners and high-level professionals, identifying a consistent need for lead generation.",
    "mvp": "Built in a month",
    "growth1": "Cold email",
    "growth2": "Email List",
    "industry": "Sales",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$199 - $399",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Three tiers: $99/mo, $199/mo, $399/mo",
    "traffic": 6242,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 9.772508811,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "How I Built A LinkedIn Outreach Tool That Generated $61K MRR Before Getting Acquired"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "name": "Gorilla ROI",
    "revenue": 500000,
    "problem": "For most Amazon sellers Manual data entry takes hours, is prone to errors, and decisions are often based on outdated information.",
    "solution": "Google Sheets add-on that connects Amazon Seller Central to Google Sheets",
    "developer": "Jae Jun",
    "ideation": "Scratching his own itch - Need to Address the inefficiencies in managing his Amazon business",
    "mvp": "Built in two months",
    "growth1": "Media Outreach",
    "growth2": "PR/Media Outreach",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Google Sheets",
    "productType": "Addon",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$199 - $399",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Their pricing has two categories: small/medium size seller plans (Starter, Pro, and Mega) starting at $97/month, and enterprise plans ranging from $347 to $797/month.",
    "traffic": 41265,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 1.009733834,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "Link #1 - Link #2 - Link #3"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "name": "Widebundle",
    "revenue": 480000,
    "problem": "Shopify merchants want to create bundles to increase AOV with the least friction possible.",
    "solution": "Shopify app that helps merchants create bundles and offers",
    "developer": "Mat De Sousa",
    "ideation": "Researching Shopify Facebook Groups to understand common problems - led to the discovery of demand for a non-existent bundled app feature.",
    "mvp": "Built in a week",
    "growth1": "Facebook",
    "growth2": "Facebook",
    "industry": "E-commerce",
    "platform": "Shopify",
    "productType": "Plugin",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Just one plan available, $18/mo",
    "traffic": 19579,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 2.043005261,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "Failing Thrice, Then Building A $40K/Month Shopify App By The Age Of 25"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "name": "Kiwi Sizing",
    "revenue": 432000,
    "problem": "Setting up size charts can get messy when you’re dealing with hundreds of different sizes from different vendors and product types.",
    "solution": "Fit recommender and size chart Shopify plugin",
    "developer": "Samping Chuang",
    "ideation": "Addressing own need - wanting to automate the tedious process of converting pet product sizes manually",
    "mvp": "Built in two months",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "E-commerce",
    "platform": "Shopify",
    "productType": "Plugin",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "A free plan and 2 Paid plans; Premium $6.99 and Ultimate plan at $12.49/month",
    "traffic": 308021,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.1168751481,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "How I Developed A $36K/Month Ecommerce Sizing Plugin "
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "name": "Sniply",
    "revenue": 420000,
    "problem": "Sharing 3rd party content on your profiles, drives traffic away from you and towards your competitors.",
    "solution": "URL shortener that adds a custom CTA button to any page you share",
    "developer": "Matt Bentley",
    "ideation": "Realization he was gaining zero ROI from the time he spent on social media - He created a tool to redirect the traffic back to his website.",
    "mvp": "Built in a couple of weeks",
    "growth1": "Content Marketing",
    "growth2": "Content Marketing",
    "industry": "Social Media",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "3 subscription options priced at $9, $29, and $59/ - based on usage and team members",
    "traffic": 18271,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 1.915603963,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "We Created A $420K/Year Tool That \"Redirects\" Website Traffic"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "name": "Mailman",
    "revenue": 360000,
    "problem": "The never-ending influx of spam and low-priority emails can overwhelm email users.\r",
    "solution": "Gmail tool that allows you to decide when and what emails should land in your inbox",
    "developer": "Mohit Mamoria",
    "ideation": "He created a script to batch emails and manage his inbox, which caught the attention of Andrew Wilkinson after sharing it",
    "mvp": "Built in eight months",
    "growth1": "Twitter",
    "growth2": "Twitter",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Gmail",
    "productType": "Plugin",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "An $8/month subscription",
    "traffic": 68984,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.4348834512,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "We Built A $360K/Year Gmail Plugin That Helps People Manage Their Inbox"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "name": "SuperLemon",
    "revenue": 348000,
    "problem": "eCommerce store owners want to connect with customers where they spend most of their time - on WhatsApp.",
    "solution": "Plugin for Shopify eCommerce stores to chat with their customers and also send order-related notifications via WhatsApp",
    "developer": "Preetam Nath",
    "ideation": "A review of the Shopify app store to identify gaps in existing apps - Eventually choose the WhatsApp idea for its unique appeal and potential.",
    "mvp": "Built in two weeks",
    "growth1": "App Store",
    "growth2": "App Store",
    "industry": "E-commerce",
    "platform": "Shopify",
    "productType": "Plugin",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Two plans, priced at $0 and $15 per montly, plus a usage fee",
    "traffic": 79285,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.365769061,
    "stillSolo": "No",
    "caseStudy": "How We Developed A $29K/Month WhatsApp Plugin For Shopify"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "name": "WP Courseware",
    "revenue": 288000,
    "problem": "Creating and selling online courses is difficult and confusing for non-technical founders.",
    "solution": "Learning Management System Plugin for WordPress",
    "developer": "Ben Arellano",
    "ideation": "A platform to launch own online course - Founders Realized there was no suitable learning management system (LMS) plugin for WordPress while launching an online course.",
    "mvp": "Built in four months",
    "growth1": "Online directories",
    "growth2": "Online Directories",
    "industry": "Software",
    "platform": "WordPress",
    "productType": "Plugin",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$99 - $199",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Per site licensing with pricing between $159 and $279/year",
    "traffic": 7932,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 3.025718608,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "How Building My Own WordPress Solution Evolved into $24K MRR"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "name": "Excelformulabot",
    "revenue": 276000,
    "problem": "Excel is a headache to learn",
    "solution": "Generates text instructions into Excel formulas within seconds with the help of AI",
    "developer": "David Bressler",
    "ideation": "The founder could not find an AI-based Excel formula generator, so he used his analytics expertise to develop one.",
    "mvp": "Built in a couple of weeks",
    "growth1": "Reddit",
    "growth2": "Reddit",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Google Sheets",
    "productType": "Addon",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "A Pro Plan with a subscription fee of $9/month ",
    "traffic": 236205,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.0973730446,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "Link #1 - Link #2 - Link#3  "
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "name": "Upvoty",
    "revenue": 240000,
    "problem": "Creators need an effective way to manage user feedback",
    "solution": "A web app for collecting and managing product feedback",
    "developer": "Mike Slaats",
    "ideation": "Scratching his own itch - He needed an affordable tool to collect and manage user feedback for his main startup, Vindy, & couldn't find any suitable options.",
    "mvp": "Launced within a day",
    "growth1": "Content marketing",
    "growth2": "Content Marketing",
    "industry": "Business",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$49 - $99",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Three tiers: $15/month, $49/month, $99/month\n14-day free trial available for each subscription tier",
    "traffic": 118846,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.1682850075,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "Why I'm Building A Side Project On Top Of My Already Successful Business"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "name": "ReferralHero",
    "revenue": 216000,
    "problem": "Founders need an easy to set up and streamlined referral program.\n",
    "solution": "Allow businesses to create highly customizable referral programs unique to their customer base",
    "developer": "Manuel Frigerio",
    "ideation": "A customer suggested a feature for attracting more attendees to events",
    "mvp": "Built in 4 days",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Marketing",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Widget",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$99 - $199",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Three tiers: $69/month, $169/month, $299/month",
    "traffic": 16526,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 1.089192787,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "How I Created A $18K/Month Referral Marketing Software"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "name": "Plasfy",
    "revenue": 180000,
    "problem": "New and non-technical founders need an easy to use online design tool",
    "solution": "All-in-one easy-to-use online design software",
    "developer": "Jasper Cyan",
    "ideation": "Frustration with existing design tools and the positive feedback from an email shared with graphic designers.\n",
    "mvp": "Built in 3 months",
    "growth1": "Cold email",
    "growth2": "Email List",
    "industry": "Graphic Design",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Pasfy has a free plan, and also two paid versions priced at $9 and $12/mo",
    "traffic": 20902,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.7176346761,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "Frustrated With The Existing Design Tools, I Built A $180K/Year Design Software"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "name": "SiteGPT",
    "revenue": 180000,
    "problem": "Custom-built bots are finicky and difficult to maintain\r",
    "solution": "AI tool to create and train web chatbots",
    "developer": "Bhanu Teja Pachipulusu",
    "ideation": "Started as a side project and as one of the features for his other product.",
    "mvp": "Built in 2 weeks",
    "growth1": "Twitter",
    "growth2": "Twitter",
    "industry": "Customer Support",
    "platform": "OpenAI",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$400+",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Two plans, priced at $99 and $999 per month. Plus an optional $50/mo addon to remove branding",
    "traffic": 79462,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.1887694747,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "How My AI Side Project Grew To $15K MRR In Just A Few Months"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "name": "ShipFast",
    "revenue": 600000,
    "problem": "Building SaaS, AI tool, or any other web app can take pretty long especially for non-technical founders and beginners.\n\n",
    "solution": "The NextJS boilerplate supercharges app development so you launch faster and make money fast",
    "developer": "Marc Lou",
    "ideation": "A Tweet from Pieter Levels about building startups independently motivated him to start his own journey.",
    "mvp": "Built in a week ",
    "growth1": "Twitter",
    "growth2": "Twitter",
    "industry": "Software",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$99 - $199",
    "businessModel": "One-Time Payment",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Two plans priced at $169 and $199.",
    "traffic": 385400,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.1297353399,
    "stillSolo": "Yes",
    "caseStudy": "How Marc Lou, PH's maker of the year, makes $50k+ every month with multiple products!"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "name": "Remote OK",
    "revenue": 2000000,
    "problem": "Remote workers need a platform that makes it easy to get hired",
    "solution": "A job board for remote workers",
    "developer": "Pieter Levels",
    "ideation": "Recognizing the difficulty people had in finding remote jobs due to the lack of centralized listings on major job boards.",
    "mvp": "Built in 1 year",
    "growth1": "Product Hunt",
    "growth2": "Product Hunt",
    "industry": "E-commerce",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "",
    "businessModel": "One-Time Payment",
    "freePlan": "",
    "pricingDetails": "",
    "traffic": 497000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.3353454058,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "Breakdown of Pieter Levels' businesses"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "name": "Starter Story",
    "revenue": 1000000,
    "problem": "Millions of people are searching realistic and actionable guidance on making extra money through side hustles.",
    "solution": "A website decicated to help people start a business.",
    "developer": "Pat Walls",
    "ideation": "Pivoting from a failed business and inspired by a Reddit post about making money online.",
    "mvp": "Built in  3 Months",
    "growth1": "Reddit",
    "growth2": "Reddit",
    "industry": "Business",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$400+",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "",
    "traffic": 1600000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.05208333333,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How I Built Starter Story"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "name": "AI Publisher Pro",
    "revenue": 360000,
    "problem": "Publishers are looking for a fast and effective content creation framework.",
    "solution": "Teaches people how to make money from AI-generated books.",
    "developer": "Joe Popelas",
    "ideation": "A revealing conversation with a successful publishing company inspired him to combine traditional publishing methods with AI technology ",
    "mvp": "Built in a month",
    "growth1": "Pinterest",
    "growth2": "Pinterest",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "$15 per month",
    "traffic": 8100,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 3.703703704,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "Meet The Kid Who Made $1M with ChatGPT\n"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "name": "Closet tools",
    "revenue": 456000,
    "problem": "Poshmark sellers want to save time and sell more than focus on engaging on the platform",
    "solution": "A web app that helps Poshmark sellers save time and sell more.",
    "developer": "Jordan O'Connor",
    "ideation": "The founder created a script to automate sharing items on Poshmark for his wife, making the process more efficient.",
    "mvp": "Built in a couple of weeks",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "$30 per month",
    "traffic": 3000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 12.66666667,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "Solving Your Spouse's Problem: A Conversation with Jordan O'Connor, Founder of Closet Tools"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "name": "MarketBeat",
    "revenue": 40000000,
    "problem": "Retail investors want an easy way to know what’s going on with their investments ",
    "solution": "A financial newsletter for retail investors",
    "developer": "Matt Paulson",
    "ideation": "The idea was to diversify traffic acquisition channels and build a content distribution network. ",
    "mvp": "Built in one year",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Finance",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$99 - $199",
    "businessModel": "One-Time Payment",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "All access @ $199",
    "traffic": 15000000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.2222222222,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How I Built A $3M/month Newsletter"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "name": "iCode This",
    "revenue": 110400,
    "problem": "Junior and aspiring coders need a platform where they can exercise their skills.",
    "solution": "A Collection of application ideas to improve coding skills",
    "developer": "Florin Pop",
    "ideation": "Founders love for coding and learning in a fun and interactive way by building projects, led him to create iCodeThis to share the fun with others!",
    "mvp": "Built in a week",
    "growth1": "Cold email",
    "growth2": "Email List",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$99 - $199",
    "businessModel": "One-Time Payment",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "",
    "traffic": 244000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.03770491803,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "Become a better developer with iCodeThis"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "name": "Headshot Pro",
    "revenue": 300000,
    "problem": "People are concerened about picture quality.",
    "solution": "AI Headshot Generator for Professional Headshots",
    "developer": "Danny Postma",
    "ideation": "The founder pivoted to developing a product similar to Dreambooth's AI service, inspired by the potential in transforming faces.",
    "mvp": "Built within 30 hours.",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Software",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2C",
    "priceRange": "",
    "businessModel": "",
    "freePlan": "",
    "pricingDetails": "Three plans: $29, $39, & $49.",
    "traffic": 222000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.1126126126,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How Danny Built HeadshotPro To $96K Business Solo"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "name": "JetPrint",
    "revenue": 8400000,
    "problem": "e-commerce sellers need a quick and efficient print on demand tool. ",
    "solution": "Offers print-on-demand services to global e-commerce sellers and consumers.",
    "developer": "Mark",
    "ideation": "The rising demand for personalization led him to focus on the print-on-demand industry.",
    "mvp": "Built in 45 days",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Graphic Design",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "Free",
    "businessModel": 2,
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Free",
    "traffic": 263000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 2.661596958,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How I Started A $8.4M/Year Print On Demand Company [From China] "
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "name": "Unicorn Platform",
    "revenue": 168000,
    "problem": "Startup founders and marketers looking for an easy & fast way to build landing pages",
    "solution": "An AI website builder",
    "developer": "Alexander Isora",
    "ideation": "Realized startup founders and marketers struggled to build landing pages & needed an easier solution to this problem.",
    "mvp": "Built in 160 hours",
    "growth1": "Product Hunt",
    "growth2": "Product Hunt",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Three plans: $9, $29, & $49.",
    "traffic": 125400,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.1116427432,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How I Launched A $2.5K/Month Landing Page Builder"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "name": "Stripo",
    "revenue": 4800000,
    "problem": "Marketers need an email template builder that is simple yet allows building advanced emails with no coding skills at all",
    "solution": "An intuitive and simple yet flexible email template creator",
    "developer": "Dmitry Kudrenko",
    "ideation": "He identified the challenge marketers face in coding HTML emails and decided to create an editor that simplifies email creation without requiring technical skills.",
    "mvp": "Built in a year",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$49 - $99",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Three Plans: $15, $45 & $95.",
    "traffic": 726000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.5509641873,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How We Grew Our Email Template Builder From 0 To 1M Users [$400K MRR] "
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "name": "ThirstySprout",
    "revenue": 2500000,
    "problem": "Finding engineers online sucks",
    "solution": "Uses AI and a database of pre-vetted candidates to help companies hire in a matter of days instead of months",
    "developer": "David Stepania",
    "ideation": "Solving a familiar problem — helping others find trusted top technical talent for their projects.",
    "mvp": "Built in 6 months",
    "growth1": "Cold Email",
    "growth2": "Email List",
    "industry": "Business",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "Free",
    "businessModel": "One-Time Payment",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "",
    "traffic": "",
    "revenuePerTraffic": "#DIV/0!",
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "Starting A $2.5M/Year Top-Tier Technical Talent Marketplace From Scratch "
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "name": "Queue",
    "revenue": 1596000,
    "problem": "Creators of productized services prefer having  payment plans, project management, to files in one central place for their clients.",
    "solution": "SaaS platform that turns a website into a software-enabled platform complete with a client portal, project management, etc.",
    "developer": "Masud Hossain",
    "ideation": "Solving own problem-initially created a basic video feedback tool for personal use, which gained popularity among esports coaches and later video editors through sharing with friends on Discord servers, revealing unmet needs in different markets.",
    "mvp": "Built in 2 weeks",
    "growth1": "Discord",
    "growth2": "Discord",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "2 plans: $49/month $ Enterprise Plan",
    "traffic": 9500,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 14,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "Our SaaS is Backed by Y Combinator and Grew to $1.6M ARR "
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "name": "Boot dev",
    "revenue": 1320000,
    "problem": "Aspiring creators are seeking practical learning opportunities to gain experience in backend development.\r\n",
    "solution": "A platform to learn in-demand back-end technologies like Python, SQL, and Go",
    "developer": "Lane Wagner",
    "ideation": "Noticed a decline in the quality of front-end developers due to the proliferation of short-term learning solutions; recognized the need for a solid foundation in backend development.",
    "mvp": "Built in a couple of months",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "E-commerce",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2C",
    "priceRange": "$199 - $399",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "Starts @ $49/month",
    "traffic": 337000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.3264094955,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How We Launched Backend Development Courses That Generate $110K/Month"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "name": "Talent Service",
    "revenue": 180000,
    "problem": "Job seekers are looking for a good employer fit & companies struggling with frequent turnover and inefficient recruitment processes.\r\n\r\n",
    "solution": "A revolutionary developer-focused platform for employer assessment and remote recruitmen",
    "developer": "Pavel Podkorytov",
    "ideation": "Observing the challenges faced by IT specialists in the recruitment process.\n",
    "mvp": "Built in 3 months",
    "growth1": "Content marketing",
    "growth2": "Content Marketing",
    "industry": "E-commerce",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "",
    "businessModel": "Affiliates",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Commission based ",
    "traffic": "",
    "revenuePerTraffic": "#DIV/0!",
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "My Remote IT Recruitment Platform Reached $15K/Month In Just 3 Months"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "name": "Bounce",
    "revenue": 300000,
    "problem": "Carrying luggage through the city can be time-consuming and inconvenient.\r\n",
    "solution": "Bounce is a short term storage marketplace",
    "developer": "Cody Candee",
    "ideation": "Observing the recurring problem of people being inconvenienced by their belongings during travel and daily activities.",
    "mvp": "Built in 3 hours",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Travel",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Mobile App",
    "target": "B2C",
    "priceRange": "Free",
    "businessModel": "",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Price depends on storage duration.",
    "traffic": 1000000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.025,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How I Turned A $5 Google Ad Into A Million Dollar Startup"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "name": "Bank Statement Converter",
    "revenue": 126000,
    "problem": "Converting PDF to spreadsheet accurately can be difficulty to achieve.",
    "solution": "The world's most trusted bank statement converter\r",
    "developer": "Angus Cheng",
    "ideation": "Solving own problem - Challenge of extracting transaction data from PDFs provided by their bank, led to creation of a web app simlifying process for others.",
    "mvp": "Built in 10 hours",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Finance",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "4 plans: $15, $30, $50/Month and Enterprise plan",
    "traffic": 22500,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.4666666667,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How I Attracted Users To My $12.5K MRR Bank Statement Converter Software "
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "name": "ReviewsOnMyWebsite\n",
    "revenue": 492000,
    "problem": "Entrepreneurs want to collect, analyze online reputation and share reviews conveniently.",
    "solution": "An online reputation management software",
    "developer": "Vitaly Motuz",
    "ideation": "solving a friend's problem -  trying to embed Google reviews on a friend's accounting firm website, realizing there was no easy solution available to showcase social proof and build trust online for businesses.",
    "mvp": "5 weeks to build",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Marketing",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Extension",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "4 plans: $9, $29, $59, and $99 per month.",
    "traffic": 60700,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.6754530478,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How This Self-Taught Developer Built A $492K/Year Reputation Management Platform"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "name": "MentorCruise",
    "revenue": 480000,
    "problem": "Good mentors are hard to find, getting them to commit is even harder.",
    "solution": "A trusted source for mentorships & coaching",
    "developer": "Dominic Monn",
    "ideation": "Personal experience - Recognizing the significant gap in mentorship availability",
    "mvp": "",
    "growth1": "Cold Email",
    "growth2": "Email List",
    "industry": "E-commerce",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "",
    "businessModel": "",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "",
    "traffic": "",
    "revenuePerTraffic": "#DIV/0!",
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How I Built A $24K/Month Mentorship Marketplace"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "name": "NoteForms",
    "revenue": 174000,
    "problem": "Notion users who want to create a form in 3 minutes and receive responses directly in their favorite productivity tool.",
    "solution": "A SaaS company offering a form builder integration to Notion",
    "developer": "Julien Nahum",
    "ideation": "Inspired by the similarities between Notion and Airtable databases.",
    "mvp": "4 days to build",
    "growth1": "Product Hunt",
    "growth2": "Product Hunt",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "3 plans: Free, $20 & $50 per month.",
    "traffic": 4600000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.003152173913,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How I Bootstrapped My Notion Form Builder $180K ARR "
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "name": "Buttondown",
    "revenue": 180000,
    "problem": "Developers looking for a nicer, simpler way to grow and manage a newsletter",
    "solution": "A simple newsletter software",
    "developer": "Justin Duke",
    "ideation": "Created the tool to fulfill his own need for a simple email tool after finding existing options either too complex or too controlling.\n",
    "mvp": "Built in a year",
    "growth1": "onlline directories",
    "growth2": "Online Directories",
    "industry": "Software",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$49 - $99",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "6 different plans that range from free to $139/mo, based on the number of subscribers",
    "traffic": 257732,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.05819999069,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "Bootstrapping A [Profitable] $15K/Month Simple Newsletter SaaS With No Experience"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "name": "CraftMyPDF",
    "revenue": 180000,
    "problem": "Business owners looking to automate content generation for their business workflows",
    "solution": "They offer API-based products which allow businesses to generate PDF documents and images from reusable templates",
    "developer": "Jacky Tan",
    "ideation": "Scratching own itch - Existing tools lacked a user-friendly template editor so he decided to develop own PDF generation services with a template editor.",
    "mvp": "Built in 3 months",
    "growth1": "SEO",
    "growth2": "SEO",
    "industry": "Business",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$99 - $199",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Four tiers: Free, $35/mo, $85/mo, $259/mo.",
    "traffic": 15395,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.9743423189,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "I Faced This Problem Firsthand And Built A $15K MRR PDF-Generation API Tool"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "name": "FormCraft",
    "revenue": 160000,
    "problem": "Building forms is often overwhelming process for founders and WordPress Users.",
    "solution": "A premium WordPress form builder",
    "developer": "Nishant",
    "ideation": "He noticed a form builder plugin with an outdated interface on CodeCanyon.net and decided he could create something better.",
    "mvp": "6 Months to build",
    "growth1": "Marketplace",
    "growth2": "Marketplace",
    "industry": "Software",
    "platform": "WordPress",
    "productType": "Plugin",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "One-Time Payment",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "One-time licensing $30",
    "traffic": 5000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 2.666666667,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How I Supported Myself Full Time by Building a WordPress Plugin"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "name": "Analyzify",
    "revenue": 144000,
    "problem": "Shopify merchants want an easy way to get valuable insights from Shopify data",
    "solution": "Data tracking app for Shopify merchants",
    "developer": "Erman Kuplu",
    "ideation": "A  high demand for data-analytics-related projects from Shopify stores.",
    "mvp": "Built in 3 months",
    "growth1": "YouTube",
    "growth2": "YouTube",
    "industry": "E-commerce",
    "platform": "Shopify",
    "productType": "Plugin",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$400+",
    "businessModel": "One-Time Payment",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "One-time $749 purchase with lifetime access and support",
    "traffic": 5000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 2.4,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "Our Analytics App For Shopify Reached $12K MRR In Just 7 Months"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "name": "Client Portal",
    "revenue": 132000,
    "problem": "Managing clients projects can get messy",
    "solution": "A lightweight project management tool for WordPress",
    "developer": "Laura Elizabeth",
    "ideation": "Scratching own itch - couldnt find an effective client management portal she built one",
    "mvp": "Built in months",
    "growth1": "Media outreach",
    "growth2": "PR/Media Outreach",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "WordPress",
    "productType": "Plugin",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$199 - $399",
    "businessModel": "One-Time Payment",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "User-based licensing starting at $199 for single site and $399 for multi site.  ",
    "traffic": 8726,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 1.260600504,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "How I Built A $7K/Month WordPress Plugin Because I Needed The Product"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "name": "Leave Me Alone",
    "revenue": 120000,
    "problem": "Email users often want a simple tool for decluttering inbox and staying free from useless emails.",
    "solution": "A service to easily unsubscribe from unwanted emails",
    "developer": "Danielle Johnson",
    "ideation": "Solving own problem of managing a messy inbox without compromising their email data privacy.",
    "mvp": "Built in 7 Days",
    "growth1": "Content Marketing",
    "growth2": "Content Marketing",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Independent/Standalone",
    "productType": "Desktop/Web App",
    "target": "B2B + B2C",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "No",
    "pricingDetails": "They offer two subscriptions at $8 and $14 per month. Additionally, the app can be used during 7 days for a $6 payment",
    "traffic": 55676,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.1796106042,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": " How This Traveling Couple Built An App That Helps You Unsubscribe From Unwanted Emails -  Updates We Made That Took Us From $500/Month To $10K/Month In 3 Years "
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "name": "GoFullPage",
    "revenue": 120000,
    "problem": "Capturing a full page screenshot can often be challenging especially for content creators",
    "solution": "Full page screen capture Chrome extension",
    "developer": "Peter Coles",
    "ideation": "Scratching own back - No existing Chrome extension to screenshot an entire webpage for printing.",
    "mvp": "Built in a week",
    "growth1": "Github",
    "growth2": "Github",
    "industry": "Productivity",
    "platform": "Chrome",
    "productType": "Extension",
    "target": "B2C",
    "priceRange": "$1 - $49",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "A premium update costs $1 a month",
    "traffic": 172000,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 0.05813953488,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "Breakdown of Peter coles GoFullPage "
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "name": "Merch Wizard",
    "revenue": 120000,
    "problem": "Sellers experience frustrations managing their portfolio of products and designs across the marketplaces.\n",
    "solution": "Helps sellers on Merch by Amazon create a database of their products with Airtable",
    "developer": "Rick Blyth",
    "ideation": "The existing tool was clunky, frustrating to use, and time-consuming, so he built a Chrome extension to help frustrated sellers.",
    "mvp": "Built in 3 Months",
    "growth1": "Cold Email",
    "growth2": "Email List",
    "industry": "E-commerce",
    "platform": "Amazon",
    "productType": "Extension",
    "target": "B2B",
    "priceRange": "$99 - $199",
    "businessModel": "Subscription",
    "freePlan": "Yes",
    "pricingDetails": "Two plans: $0/forever to $15/month (or $150/year)",
    "traffic": 7810,
    "revenuePerTraffic": 1.280409731,
    "stillSolo": "",
    "caseStudy": "I Developed A Niche Chrome Extension For Amazon Merch Sellers That Makes $120K/Year"
  }
]